Hilda Mason, City Council 029
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1
  - DC Taxi Cab Commission Records 1 of 2, 1993-1995 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Public Hearing Dc. 18 1990 Bills 8-412 and 416 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Regular Meeting 11/27/89, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Committee Meeting 11/27/89 Sec. 302 Bill 8-239, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Regular Meeting 11/13/89, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Joint Roundtable w/ Hum. Serv. 11/1/89, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Reschedule Meeting: 10/16/89, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - September 25 1989 (Reg. Mtg) (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - September 13 1989 Informal Meeting of CTEE: Re: School Disposal Legislation (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - July 10 1989 ( Regular Meeting) (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - June 12 1989 (Regular Meeting/Joint Public Roundtable w/gov't ops) (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Schools systems garly out bell and mckenzie garly out bill, 1989 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Tax Reform, 1992-1995 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Children's Island Briefing Sept. 20 1995 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Clean Air Compliance Fee Act of 1994 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - Another Interstate Commuter Bridge in the District, undated (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Barny Circle Freeway Project, 1995 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Region: Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, 1989-1993 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Work Program and Budget for Fiscal Year 1994 and 1995 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Region: Metropolitan Washington Council of Governments, 1989-1993 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Work Program and Budget for Fiscal Year 1994 and 1995 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Washington Regional Directory - 1994 and 1995, 1994-1996 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - The Report of the Partnership for Regional Excellence, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Proposed Work Program and Budget for Fiscal Year 1997 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Drugs/Crime/Justice System, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Name and Address List, undated (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Extending the Legacy- Planning Americans Capital for the 21st century, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - DC Taxi Cab Commission 2 of 2, 1993-1995 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Proposed Work Program and Budget for Fiscal Year 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Traffic Adju Act, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Urban Forest Preservation, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Ctte. On Education FY '87 Pub. Hearing DCPS Budget Request. ( Cont.), 1986 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Human Services FY 1987 Budget Hearing (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Education Hearing Friday February 22 1985 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - UDC FY 1986 Budget Hearing, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Ed. Committee. Mark Up Meeting. FY '86 Supplemental. Budget Request (DCPS)6/9/86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - FY '87 Budget Requests Mark-Up Meeting March 5 1986 Ed. Ctte (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Ed. Ctte FY '86 Supplemental. Request. (DCPS) Pub Hearing 5/23/86, 1986 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  - Budget Hearing of Committee on Education DC City Council, 1985 (Box 70, Folder 20)
  - FY '86 DCPS Budget Hearings 2/13 - 14/85 Statements info 1 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 70, Folder 21)
  - FY '86 DCPS Budget Hearings 2/13 - 14/85 Statements info 2 of 2, 1985-1987 (Box 70, Folder 22)
  - Question to Board of Education, 1987 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Regular Meeting 4/23/90 Bills 8-2392416, 1990 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Meeting- Special PR 8-408 June 4 1990 Bill 18-375 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday April 23 1990 (Box 70, Folder 26)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries April 9 1990 (Box 70, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Special Mtg. 2/9/90 (Bd. Contract), 1990 (Box 70, Folder 28)
  - Regular Meeting (1/22/90), 1990 (Box 70, Folder 29)
  - Extending the Legacy- Planning Americans Capital for the 21st century, 1996 (Box 70, Folder 30)
  - B. 8-412 Conveyance of the Revoc. Ctr. For the Handicapped Property Act of '89, 1989 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - B. 8-407 DC Preschool Education Improvement Act of '8, undated (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Orientation College Bound, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - OCB - 1988 and Consultants (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Press Releases (D.C.P.L) 1 of 2, 1987-1989 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Press Releases (D.C.P.L) 2 of 2, 1987-1989 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Reclassification, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Region IV Coalition of Friends of District of Columbia Public Libraries, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Shepherd Park Library, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Spanish Speaking Services (DCPL), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Friends of Takoma Library, 1988 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Trust Funds (DCPL), 1987 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Union Agreement, 1987 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - D.C Public Lib Board of Trustees Appointment Act of 1985 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - PR 6-226 D.C Library BD William Mayo Lee Confir Res. of 1985 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - PR 6--227 DC Library BD John G. Hazel Confir Res of 1985 (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Bill 6-437 "Francis A. Gregory Region Branch Library 1 of 2 Resignation Act of '86 1 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - Bill 6-437 "Francis A. Gregory Region Branch Library 1 of 2 Resignation Act of '86 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - B. 5-104 "D.C Confidentiality of Records Act of '84, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Bill 5-214 "D.C Public Library Amended Accessory Sales Act of '83, 1978-1983 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Library Improvement Act, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - H Street Revitalization Program Business Loan Applications, undated (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Rafael L. Cortada UDC 1 of 2, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Rafael L. Cortada UDC 2 of 2, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Green, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Bob Pederson File, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - U.D.C: Presidents Reports, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - UDC Public Relations, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Labor Studies Program, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Open Admissions 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Open Admissions 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Bill 6-437 "Francis A. Gregory Region Branch Library 1 of 2 Resignation Act of '86 2 of 2, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - B. 5-104 "D.C Confidentiality of Records Act of '84, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Bill 5-214 "D.C Public Library Amended Accessory Sales Act of '83, 1978-1983 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Library Improvement Act, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - H Street Revitalization Program Business Loan Applications, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Rafael L. Cortada UDC 1 of 2, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Rafael L. Cortada UDC 2 of 2, 1987-1990 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Green, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Bob Pederson File, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - U.D.C: Presidents Reports, 1986 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - UDC Public Relations, 1988 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Labor Studies Program, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Open Admissions 1 of 2, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Open Admissions 2 of 2, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Special Programs, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Presidents Discretionary Fund (UDC), 1987 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Reorganization of UDC (1988), 1984-1988 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Tuition Bill - Kanes Amendment, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - UDC Task Force, 1989 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - John Wumble, 1985-1989 (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - HR Subtle Judiciary/Education 4/23/87 UDC Hearings, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - House Sub Ctte. On Judiciary/Education UDC Oversight 10/27/87, 1987 (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Board of Trustees- Nominations 1 of 2, 1983-1990 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Board of Trustees- Nominations 1 of 2, 1983-1990 (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - Education and libraries Public Roundtable 12/2/94, 1994 (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Education and libraries Regular Meeting 2/6/95, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Education and libraries Regular Meeting 2/6/95 1 of 2, 1992-1995 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Education and libraries Regular Meeting 2/6/95 2 of 2, 1992-1995 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Education and libraries Public Roundtable 6/8/92, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Education and libraries Public Roundtable 6/8/92, 1992 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Education and libraries Public Roundtable 6/19/92 1 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Education and libraries Public Roundtable 6/19/92 2 of 2 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Bill 8-239 "District of Columbia Compulsory School Attendance School Day Care and Evening School Use Amendment Act of 1989 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Bill 8-239 "District of Columbia Compulsory School Attendance School Day Care and Evening School Use Amendment Act of 1989 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Enabling Legislation/Committee Report D.C. School of Law 1 of 3, 1985-1989 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Enabling Legislation/Committee Report D.C. School of Law 2 of 3, 1985-1989 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Enabling Legislation/Committee Report D.C. School of Law 3 of 3, 1985-1989 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Public Roundtables Friday June 19 1992 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Schools and Medication 1 of 3, 1986-1992 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Schools and Medication 2 of 3, 1986-1992 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Schools and Medication 3 of 3, 1986-1992 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Wilmer Johnson, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Union (AFSCME), 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - UDC- Community Needs Assessment, 1988 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Washington Saturday College, 1987 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - UDC/BOTS By- Laws, 1985-1990 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - College of Engineering (UDC) Reaccreditation issue (1986) 2 of 2 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Congressional Materials of Interest to UDC, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Center for Applied Research and Urban Policy, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - UDC Images Publications 1988, 1985-1988 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Background to Engineering Accreditation Problem, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Joint Pub. Hearing. (Gov Ops and ed. Ctte) Oct. 19 1986, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Extra Copies of Engineering Documents, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Mulkirk Tract, 1986 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - UDC Developmental Education, 1972-1978 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - UDC Part Time Faculty Issues, 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - UDC RIF Summer - 1987 Rules (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - COE Regular Mtg. Oct. 26 1987 Management Plan (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Tree Act Technical Amendments Act of 1982, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Amendment Forms, 1988 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Minutes - Motions Form, 1984 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - B 7-32 Legal and Medical Education and Services Grant Program Estb. Act of 1987, undated (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - B 7-44 Merit Personnel Residency Amendment of 1987 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Board of education vacancy and special elections for imitative, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - 7-47 D.C Public School Nurse Assignment Act of 1987 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - B. 7-58 Tuition Grant for Parents Care Taker Relatives or Leg Guardians Eligible for AFDC 1 of 2, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - B. 7-58 Tuition Grant for Parents Care Taker Relatives or Leg Guardians Eligible for AFDC 2 of 2, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - 11/18/91 Roundtable on Library and Information Services Extra Copies of Reports/Testimony etc., 1991 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Education and libraries Monday November 18,1991 Public Roundtable (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries February 25 1991 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Bill 9-48, 1991 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Referral of Proposed Legislation January 18 1991 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Bill 9-48 The Board of Trustees of the University of District of Columbia Compensation Amendment Act of 1991 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday February 4 1991 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday February 4 1991 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Education Reform 1 of 2, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Education Reform 2 of 2, 1993-1994 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - November 18 1991 Roundtable on Libraries and Information Services Post D.C and White House Conference Original Notes (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Bill 10-594, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Jan and Jim File (8/31/94) 4-5-94 Prayer in Public Schools, 1994 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Law School Summer - 1994 Send notices to all three folks, 1994-1995 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Athletics, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Beth Aushbrooks Project, 1986-1987 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - UDC Board of Trustees, 1987-1990 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Community College - 1988 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Auditors Report, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - UDC Alumni Association, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - UDC Requirements for Art and Social Science Courses, 1995 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Consortium of Universities, 1986 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - UDC Enrollment Statistics, 1983-1989 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Dinner Party, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Senate UDC, 1987-1988 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Farrakhan, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - B. 7-79 D-C Higher Education Funding Program Implementation Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - 7-122 "Critical Personal Educational Grant Program Establishment Act of 1986 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - 7-123 District of Columbia Retirement Reform, 1987 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - 7-139 "Boards and Commissions Revision Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - 7-146 Nurses Training Corps Establishment Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - 7- 160 "Board of Education Capital Construction Contracting Authority Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - 7-162 "Board of Education and Capital Construction Contracting Authority Temporary Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - 7-168 "District of Columbia General Hospital Nursing Study Temporary Commission Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - 7-236 "District of Columbia School of Law Interim Board of Governors Amendment Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - 7-253 "Educational Institution Licensure Commission Institution Title Amendment Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - 7-265 " District of Columbia School of Law Site Designation Amendment Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - 7-302 "District of Columbia School of Law Establishment Second Amendment act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - 7-351 "Board of Education Residency Requirement Exemption Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Bill 7-364 Prohibition of Discrimination in the Provision of INS, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - 7-380 "District of Columbia Comprehensive Mert Personnel Act of 1978 Educational Services Amend Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - 7-393 "Repeal of the Mandatory Retirement Ace Limitation for Teacher in D.C. P.S Amend Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - 7-397 "District of Columbia Employment of Miners Act Theatrical Permit Amendment Act of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - E. 7- 470 "DC Parents in School Prog. Act of 1988 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - B. 7-582" BD of Ed Educational Serv. Comp System Emergency Act of '88, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - B. 7-583 "Bd of Ed. Educational Serv. Comp System Temp Act of '88, 1988 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - B. 7-586 "Technical Amendment Act of 1988 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - B .7-593 Early Retirement for Superintendents of Schools Act of 1988 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - B. 7-594 "Bd. Of Ed. Comp. System Emer. Act of 1988 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - PR 7-31 Board of Trustees of the Univ of D of C Arthur M Reynolds Confirmation Resolution of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - PR 7-39 Compensation Award for Empty of the D of C Bd. Of Ed. In Comp Units 6 and 17 Approval Res of 1987 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - PR 7-49 "District of Columbia Bd. Of Ed and Wash Teach - Un. local 6 - AFT Comp. Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - PR 7-77 "Bd of Ed Capital Const Contract Arthur Emergency Declare Resolution of 1987, 1987-1990 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - PR 7-245 " Peter G.W Keen Conf. Res. Of '87, 1987-1990 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - PR 7-296 Ivan Sellin Conf Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - PR 7-515 bd of Ed Comp. Emergency Declaration Resolution of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - PR 7-504 DC Bd. Of Ed. Educational Service Employees FY 89' Pay Adjustment, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - PR 7-481 D.C Board of Ed. Non Union Pay Piece, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - PR 7-480 Compen Settlt Employees in Compensation Units 6 and 17, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - PR 7-471 Concha N. Johnson Confirmation Res. UDC Bd. Trust., 1988 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - PR 7-169 Roer Wilkins Conf Rses. UDC Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - PR 7-468 Patricia A. Mathis Conf., 1988 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - PR 7-467 A Knighton Stanley UDC Board of Trustees Confirm, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - PR 7-458 Reorg. Plan 4, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - PR 7-457 DCRA and Ed Inst. Lic Comm Reorganization Plan #3, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - PR 7-455 District of Columbia School of Law New Compensation System Approval Resolution - 1988 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - PR 7-516 "Bd. Of Trustees of UDC Report Gladston Con.f Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - PR 7-517 "Submission Date for FY '90 Budget Approval Res. Of '88, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - PR 7-519 "DC Bd. Of Ed Educational Serv Employees FY 88 Pay Adjustment and Comp. System Changes App Res. Of '88, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - PR 7-524 Bd of Ed Compensation System Emer. Ded Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - PR 7-535 Compensation Award for Employees for the D.C Bd. Of Ed. In Comp Units 7 and 9 Approv. Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - PR 7-546 D.C Bd of Ed. Fed-Unit 16, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - PR 7-552 D.C BD FY 88 Pay Adj., 1988 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Education and Libraries Monday 9/26/88, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - PR 7-247 William J. Byron Conf. Res. of 1981, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - PR 7-249 "Marion O Greene Jr. Conf. Res of 1987, 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - PR 7-248 "Lois D. Rice Conf. Res of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - PR 7-250 "Morton Bahr Conf. Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - PR 7-525"Alan F. Bogatay Cong. Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - PR 7-254 "Sarah E. Melendez Conf. Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - PR 7-255 "Byron J. Grayson Conf Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - PR 7-257 "Ronald V. McGowan Conf Res of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - PR 7-258 "EPTC Bd. Of Directors Howard T. Jessamy Conf. Res of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - PR 7-259 "John V. Pollock Conf. Res. of 1987 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - PR 7-374 "EPTC Board of Directors Denis G. Elchorn Conf. Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - PR 7-376 "EPTC Board of Directors, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - PR 7-390 "Compensation Settlement for Employees in Compensation Unit 5 App Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - PR 7-417 "DC Bd. Of Lib Trustees Bessie M. Ess Conf. Res. of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - PR 7-442 Compensation Settlement for Employees in Comp Unit 18 Approval Resolution of 1988 (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Abortion, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - Advisory Commission on Poster Education, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Aid - Grants to Schools, 1981-1983 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Aids in Public Schools, 1986-1988 (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - American Association of University Women, 1989 (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Adult Education, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - American Federation of Teachers, 1987 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - Asbestos, 1982-1988 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Attendance Issues, 1986 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Banneker School, 1984-1988 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - Bilingual Education, 1985 (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - Black Youth Unemployment, 1983 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Bd. Of Ed. Members' Elections info etc., 1985-1990 (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - D.C Board of Ed. Meeting 12/15/88, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - Board of Education 7/27/88 Meeting, 1988 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - D.C.P.S Community- Gram - 1987-1988 (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - Buildings- Rent Collection Rental Income and other reports from Bd. Of Ed, 1982-1990 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Buildings - Rent Collection (Statutes /Rules), 1982 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Buildings - Rent Collection (Questions from Prior Years), 1986 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - COE Meeting at Buses, undated (Box 81, Folder 4)
  - Capital Improvements Programs (DCPS), 1982 (Box 81, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Foundation, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - Catholic Schools, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - Children's Defense Funds, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 8)
  - Cleveland Elem School Grover, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - Competency - Based Curriculum, 1981 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - Computers, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - Concerned Student Loan Program 1 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - Concerned Student Loan Program 2 of 2, 1984-1985 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Letters, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - Curricula, 1985 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - Pledge of Allegiance Schools, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - Day Care, 1980-1989 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - D.C Advisory Ctte in Ed. 1 of 2, 1986-1989 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - D.C Advisory Ctte in Ed. 2 of 2, 1986-1989 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - D.C Community on Education, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 20)
  - Building and Grounds (DCPS), 1983-1987 (Box 81, Folder 21)
  - Eastern High School, 1988 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - US Department of Education, 1986-1989 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - DCPS Income Rental Reports, 1986 (Box 81, Folder 24)
  - Desegregation, 1982 (Box 81, Folder 25)
  - Parent/Community Awareness, 1983 (Box 81, Folder 26)
  - Florett Dukes McKenzie, 1986-1987 (Box 81, Folder 27)
  - Educational Consolidation and improvement Act of 1983 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1983-1988 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Education Commission of the States, 1984-1987 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Educational Institutional Licensure Commission, 1985-1988 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - Educational Opportunity Center, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - On Peace and Education, 1989 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - College Tuition, 1988-1990 (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Annual Budget Program Measures - 1988 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - FY 89' Appropriations Act 1 of 4, 1988-1989 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - FY 89' Appropriations Act 2 of 4, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - FY 89' Appropriations Act 3 of 4, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - FY 89' Appropriations Act 4 of 4, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Budget Request 1 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Budget Request 2 of 2, 1988-1989 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - FY 89 Budget - Press Articles, 1988 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - FY 88 Budget: Budget Structure, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - ACLU - Vending Machine Regulations Proposal, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Press Clippings (Misc. Non-District Budget Forms), 1987 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - FY 88 Budget: General Staff Notes on Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - FY 88 Budget, 1980-1987 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - FY 88 Budget, 1980-1987 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - FY 88 Budget: Law School/Libraries EPTC 2/25/87 Public Hearing, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - FY 88 Budget Mark up Mtg. March 3 1987 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - FY 88 Budget: CTTE Report, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Staff Notes on Budget Issues, 1986-1987 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Private Citizen Correspondence 1 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Private Citizen Correspondence 2 of 2, 1987-1988 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Committee Questions 1 of 2, 1987 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Committee Questions 2 of 2, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Ed. Ctte. Follow up Questions 2/23/87, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Follow up Questions For Board (At Regular CTTE Mtg. 2/25/87, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - FY 88 Budget: DCPS Press Clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - 2/13/87 DCPS FY 88-Public Hearing Staff Notes /Copies of Extra Testimony 1 of 2, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - 2/13/87 DCPS FY 88-Public Hearing Staff Notes /Copies of Extra Testimony 2 of 2, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - UDC FY 1988 Budget: Staff Notes, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - UDC FY 1988 Budget: Government Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - UDC FY 1988 Budget: Private Correspondence, 1987 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - UDC FY1988 Budget: Questions and Answers, 1986-1987 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - UDC FY 1988 Budget: Press Clippings, 1986-1987 (Box 83, Folder 11)